よみがえった王は 自らをメルエムと名乗り
They are definitely coming!
何が起こってるの？
Yeah, an item sold for ten thousand can be turned around for a
hundred million the next day.
総帥様は　どこ？
You can make a fortune instantly. It's where dreams come true. Wow...
あれは敵の能力。
Anyway, do you think Kurapika
and Leorio will show up?
敵本体にダメージを与えなければ 恐らく消えませぬ。
They promised to meet us here. I'm sure they'll come. Yeah.
ほう　面白い。
They might try to contact us.
試すか。
Hey, you have to buy a phone!
おぉ。
It's standard Hunter gear.
まさに　あれは俺の…
Ah, that's true. Hey! Welcome! This one's great...
おぉ…。
That model is for people
who only make calls.
う…。
Leorio! Yo! I would recommend...
なるほど。
It's a little heavy and pricey, but it includes a translator for the
two hundred languages used worldwide. What? Seriously?
我の能力　我のためにあらず
Go with this one. I'll buy one, too! Yeah!
王にお渡しするための ものだったのだ！
Two, please. Two will cost four hundred thousand. Four hundred thousand?
ユピー。 はっ！
That's expensive, pops!
理屈に合わぬな。
Thanks, Leorio!
うぅ… あ…
But, damn, 110,580 Jenny apiece, huh?
攻撃した相手に憑く能力を 知っていたということは
It's a new model, so that's a
fair price in this market. Still, talk about overkill.
間近で　それを実際に見たか お主自身が その能力を受けたかのいずれか。
I've never seen a cell phone purchase greeted
with applause before. But you really saved us.
どちらだ？
Just so you know, that was nothing.
私が攻撃を受けました。
He's the last person you
would find at an auction.
今現在　お主に あれは憑いていない。
So how are you guys doing? What do you mean? You've trained and gotten stronger, right?
なのに　なぜ敵は生きている？
What?!
お主は　どうやって 敵の能力を解除したのだ？
You returned the tag to
Hisoka at Heavens Arena? And you have to be pretty good
to make it to the 200s...
答えよ。
How strong have you gotten now? Hey, did you learn Nen, Leorio?
条件を交わしました。
Yeah, you bet. Awesome!
あの能力を 解除すれば　仲間を助けると。
Really? Why would I lie to you? It's the ability to build up a shroud
of aura, one's own life force...
仲間もろとも 始末することはできたはず。
That's Ten, one of the four major
principles for learning Nen.
なぜ　しなかった？
Eh? There's more to it?
恐らく　敵の何かに 負けたくなかったのだと。
Greed Island ? What's that? A legendary game. We're trying to get a copy at the auction.
たとえ敵とはいえ
But why a game?
その場で約束を破棄にすることは 敗北に感じたのです。
I think this game holds a
clue to finding my dad. Huh?
ばかな！
The game holds a clue to finding your dad?
そんな あやふやな個人的感情が理由で
What do you mean? Well, it's a long story.
王に牙むく者どもを　むざむざ 見過ごしたというのですか？
Anyway, the problem is the cost. How much are we talking? The lowest starting bid is
返す言葉はございませぬ。
8.9 billion?! How much do you have? We made some bad investments, so we're down to 5 million.
余は偽るなと命じただけ。
Listen up, kids... This event is held at Southern Piece,
the world's finest auction house.
それに対し　真実で応えた者に とがの　あろうはずもない。
The money you have won't
cover the entry fee.
あぁ…。
But the game has a low difficulty rank
on the Hunter site's treasure list.
プフ！ はっ！ ユピー！
Really? Because you only need
money to get a copy.
はっ！
It always comes back to money.
お互い　不便な体になったな。
This world runs on money! Well...
我らは　肉体も心も つながってしまった。 ３名の間で もはや　隠し事は　かなわぬぞ。
That just means that a real
treasure can't be bought. If you can't obtain an item
like this with ease, you can't be considered
a pro Hunter, right?
王！
But first, we need money...
王。 行くぞ。
We'll need some starting funds.
はっ！
Let's find a way to make
some money in Yorknew!
その　後ろめたさの感情に 感づいての
Damn! What's wrong?! I created a complete
duplicate of the program.
最後の忠告でしょうか？
Why aren't any events being triggered?
それでも！ たとえ死罪になろうとも！
Did Kil somehow trick me? No... No way.
王のため！
He isn't capable of creating a fake game, and he's not stupid enough
to lie over a deal.
生物統一のため！
I want to know the answer. I'll do whatever it takes to
uncover this secret...
あれは　いらぬ！ それが王のため
I have 12.7 billion left. I'll need at least twice that amount
違う　こっちだ。
to guarantee a winning bid...
へい！ あっ！
Dad, I want to make a deal.
ばらけてちゃ 俺にダメージ与えられねえぜ？
I'll kill fifteen people,
so lend me 15 billion. Got it. Bye.
ん？
Autopilot engaged to Lingon Airport.
シカトか！　待て　こら！ 俺とやんなきゃ ポットクリンは取れねえぞ！
I think I was ten...
ユピー！ 突然　敵が目の前に現れました！
The last time I went outside. Huh? Swap?
あれを憑けた奴は 瞬間移動もできるんですか？
What does that mean?
別の奴だ。
"Swap."
自分と　その周囲を 透明にできる奴がいる。
An auction technique. Slang for the exchange of goods.
カメレオンみたいな奴だ。
Also see "Bind." What's a bind?
名前は知らねえが　師団長の１人 つまり裏切り者だ！
"Bind." The seller names a condition
besides money as their price.
人間はおろか 裏切り者まで見逃した ということですか？　あなたは！
The winning bid will be the
one that comes closest to meeting that condition.
うぅ…　どんな罰でも受ける。
Condition? No idea what that means.
王！　この件は　奴らを倒し次第…。
So that's it...
構わぬ　不問だ。
There's another kind of auctioning...
これはむしろ　我々キメラが 進化する過程において 乗り越えねばならぬ試練とみた。
Tonight, at 9 PM, the mummy of Princess Corco
will be auctioned off.
ユピー　お主の精神的揺らぎも 裏切り者の心変りも
Ivlenkov, Tocino, and Baise, you'll handle the bidding. Will three people be enough? Each group of bidders
is limited to three people.
受け入れた上で　次へ進む。
You cannot bring weapons,
recorders, or communication devices.
人は我々が　さらなる次元へ 上るための　いけにえ。 最高のな。
All on-site security is handled by
the Mafia that runs the auction, so there's rarely any trouble.
我らに残る　人の我の残滓など
to turn every Mafia member,
worldwide, against you.
さまつな不確定要素にすぎぬ。
This auction is built on trust.
王の意見が爆発の前後で １８０度　違うのも
Which is why the Mafia don't
use security cameras. The unspoken rule is that
衝撃によるものか
any grudges and the like are left outside.
否！　どちらも王
Which means that if anything does happen, their testimony will decide everything.
敵の能力が 透明ならば　触れれば分かる
Their words are treated as gospel.
分身として ものが見える 限界まで細かく分散し
So it's imperative to make
a good impression.
探索範囲を拡大！
Don't start any petty fights. Avoid talking to anyone
outside this group.
野郎　完全に標的は 俺じゃ　ねえ
What about the rest of us? Basho and Linssen will cover the rear entrance.
急に引き返して来て 一体　誰を狙ってる？
Kurapika and Melody will
take the front entrance. Squala and I will guard the lady.
やはり 裏切り者のメレオロンか？ なら　絶対ヤバい！
And with that, the mission begins.
絶対に　メレオロンを死守する
Come on down! Let's have some
conditional auctioning fun!
細かく分裂したら　プフの分身は 見えなくなってしまった
A diamond worth three million. Comes with the appraisal of the
store where I just bought it.
本体と違って　分身のほうは
Arm wrestling will decide the winning bid.
実物大でないと 捉えられないのだわ
The first person to beat this
boy wins the diamond.
突然　現れたリーゼントは 明らかに　おとり
Now, let's start the auction! Yeah! It's mine! I'm in!
私達が　カメレオンを 裏切り者と認識したことは
Count me in! Okay, don't push... Form a line.
あちらも承知でしょう つまり　私が 裏切り者を処分するため
Adjust your strength to
match the opponent.
戻って来たと奴らは考える
Every now and then,
pretend to be struggling.
仮に現在　カメレオンが 周りの者を透明にしながら
Okay, you're first! You need to pay the entry fee up front.
逃亡　潜伏しており その中に　あの娘がいるとしても
Here you go... 10,000 Jenny. Thank you, step right up!
追い詰められれば カメレオンをかばい 娘を置いて行くはず
Okay, clasp hands.
なぜならば　私が狙っているのは カメレオンだと思っているから
Just follow my instructions. Are you ready?
ピトーが 必死に治療していた娘を
You get a single round! Ready...
私が殺しに戻るなど 想像すらできないはず
Go!
より好都合！
Uh-oh!
あちらから　条件付きで
Will he do it?
娘を　私に差し出すことすら 期待できます
You almost have it... Hang in there!
確かめてみようぜ。
Oh, so close! Damn, I lost to a little kid...
ハッ！
I get it.
地下倉庫への扉…
But to reach 8.9 billion, we're going to need 889,999 wins. Damn...
なるほど　私に透明能力が バレていることも承知の
And you lose! Next, please.
二者択一ということですね
You lose!
私の分身を　さらに分散し 弱体化させようという作戦
He's gotta be running out of steam. He looks tired,
and he's sweating hard. Don't lose before I get my turn!
いや　あっち あっち　あっち！
I feel bad about tricking everyone. I'm even breaking out in a cold sweat
あっ！
at the idea of making so
much money so easily.
二択は二択
Let's have a fair contest.
だが　裏切り者か娘かの二択？
Oh, yes.
私のターゲットが　どちらなのか 判断するのが狙いか
Ready... Go!
目的は　こっちか！ 娘を殺し　しばらく王の目に 触れぬ所に隠すだけなら
Oh, too bad! You lose! Good job, girl! Thank you very much.
分身でもできる！
Oh, you're welcome.
１２分で！
A pity.
こいつ…
Well? I lost.
とんでもなく…
He's strong. That little boy?
速い こっちが本命か？
I sort of wanted that diamond.
鬼ごっこなら付き合うぜ。
You should've used your left hand. Yes, why didn't you use
your stronger hand?
ひと晩中でもな。
Oh, right...
くっ…　あの反応の速さ
He extended his right hand,
so I did the same. I'd like to challenge him again.
全力の私でも 捕らえることは困難か…
You can't. No time. We have our job. Yes.
早くしないと王が着く！
Besides, buying and
bidding would be wrong.
どうする？
We're thieves.
窮地の中　思い立つ　悪魔の策
If we want something, we take it.
あった！
No way! I'm going!
最高の魔法！
Can you hear me?
I'm ready to give up...
敵の手に渡すわけには いかない！
Yes, her tantrum—
そうだわ　追ってる人の声は
That is, her crying exhausted her,
and she's asleep now.
総帥様のおそばにいた人のもの ならば　王とは総帥様のこと じゃあ　この人は… この人の仲間は一体…
I don't know what will
happen when she wakes. I vow to obtain the items she desires, but her goal is to participate
in the bidding personally. So she'll be disappointed
あなた方のゆがんだ正義感は 決して人民のためにならない！
when she wakes up and realizes
that she missed her chance. Very well.
まずは　娘に魔法をかける
I'll adjust my schedule and
head over personally.
猜疑心を呼び起こす 魔法の言葉 王も我々も
For now, just be sure to get
that mummy princess, so we can get Neon in a good mood again.
対話による歩み寄りを 望んでいます！
Understood.
今すぐ彼女を解放しなさい！ 野郎　好き勝手ほざきやがって 何　考えてんだ？
It's me. How's it going? Nothing unusual.
離すて。 え？
No changes visible from the outside.
ワダすを降ろすてください！
Understood.
あなた変です！ 痛っ！
We'll notify you if anything happens.
何かビリビリするす！ ちょっ…　えっ！
Still, they're being quite thorough.
何言ってんだ　ばか！ 俺は　あんたを助けに来たんだぞ！
Only Mafia security are allowed
ウソです！
within five hundred meters
of the auction house.
ウソって…　お前　俺より あの虫　信じんのかよ？ 虫？　何言ってんですか あなたこそ！
If they didn't do that, the surroundings
would be crawling with thugs.
くっ…　そうだ こいつ　目が見えねえんだ
They're practically announcing that
unwholesome practices are going on.
説明できねえかも
I suppose so.
うわ！
Will the Phantom Troupe
チッ　惜しい
really show up?
クッフフ… いとも簡単に毒は回った
Hmm?
背負った娘が抵抗すれば あなたの素早さも半減
That's the same sound I heard earlier.
どういうことだ？ 今　確かに俺じゃなく
You see, I happened to see you
leaving the Hunter agency.
殺すつもりで
When you walked past me, your heart was playing a melody of rage.
逃げられて　よし
May I ask you a question?
抵抗してガキが　ひるんだ隙に
Yes.
娘を殺せば　なお　よし
Scarlet eyes. Exactly what...
コムギさん！　賊にとって あなたは大事な人質！
do they mean to you?
決して 殺されることはありません！
Why do you ask?
もっと動いて！　もっと暴れて！
No real reason.
すぐ助けます！
Curiosity?
ハッ！
When you saw the image
on the data card, your heartbeat was even more fearsome.
寝かしたから無理。 まっ　そっちの事情は 知んねえけど
It played a melody of boundless fury.
てめぇが　ムカつくってことは 十分　分かった。
I suppose that I can't lie...
この「円」の中に入ったら
Our eyes are normally brown, but they're red when we're excited.
殺す。
So I wear black contacts
to avoid discovery.
タァ！
I am searching for the eyes taken from my brethren.
分身つってもさ 元は全部　お前の細胞だろ？
Will you report this to Dalzollene?
焼け焦げれば　そこは死ぬ。
I will not. I do not wish to be killed.
電撃…
You could read my intention? A heartbeat is always honest.
来いよ… そぎ取って　はぜてやるから。 くっ…。 苦戦しているのか？ あっ！
When you began to confess
your true nature to me, your heartbeat was calm, but frigid.
焦燥が伝わって来るが。 手を貸すぞ？
The heartbeat of one who is prepared to kill.
ご心配には及びません。 メルエム様は　何よりも ご記憶の回復が最優先。
Your heart said that, though you would hold
no grudges, I was fair game if I talked. Why did you take this job?
賊ごとき 本体が戻れば問題ありません。
Why do you ask? I'll probably lie.
それよりも ご覧ください　メルエム様！
I'll know if you're lying by your eyes.
思い出されましたか？
I'm also a pro Hunter...
全ては王のため！
A Music Hunter, I suppose.
全てが王のもの！ これが余の…。
I'm looking for a certain musical score.
これら 知恵回らぬ下層愚民を統べ 生物山脈の頂に立つことこそ
You aren't lying, but you are concealing
something important.
王　本来の光あふれる宿命！ 天務にございます！
Well, let's just say that you're correct.
何かが違う。 はっ？
A solo said to have been
composed by the devil.
余は…
There are four versions...
For the piano, violin, flute, and harp.
まだ　他に何か これではない何かを…。
If a human plays or listens to the piece, it's said that disaster will befall them.
あっ！
Isn't that just a myth?
生物大統一より 大切な目標などあろうはずが…。
I doubt something like that
could exist in reality.
痛みが引かぬ
I've heard the flute version.
敵との攻防で…。
My friend who played the piece died,
their entire body like this.
メルエム様が 宮殿を出た後のことです。
That friend learned a single
movement from someone
余が　いつもいた場所は　どこだ？
who said never to play the music.
今は崩れて　跡形もなく。
That day, we were drunk and giddy. My body was destroyed, but I
gained this ability in return.
残った所を見てみるか。 はっ！　何か記憶の 手掛かりになるようなものが
However, I wish to restore my body.
見つかるかもしれませぬ。
I'm willing to do anything.
ハッ！
I don't want anyone else
to end up like me.
うぅ…　まずい
So I'll find the score and destroy it.
なり得る…　軍儀の盤や駒が…
I chose this job because
記憶を呼び起こす鍵に！
it will be more efficient to
work from the underworld.
回収処分せねば　全て！
It's time.
あそこだ。
How will Kurapika, now a
Nostrade Family bodyguard, deal with them?